gulahmedshop.com 2015-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Gul Ahmed

Thank you for visiting our web site. Gul Ahmed values the relationship we have with our customers and we are committed to responsible information handling practices. Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted.

## Collection of Information

We collect personal information such as your contact information (name, e-mail address, etc.), and billing/shipping information (credit card number, shipping address, etc.) We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input at 128-bit strength. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. It is not disclosed to any third party in any way that personally identifies you.

## Cookie and Tracking Technology

This site may use cookie and tracking technology, depending on the features offered. A cookie is a small data file that a web site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your hard drive. This will enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide features such as the storage of items in your Shopping Cart. No personal information is stored in these cookies. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to complete your transactions on this web site. We recommend that you leave them turned on or contact our Customer Service to have your order placed.

Our web site may also use other technologies to track pages on our web site that our visitors view; for gathering information such as browser type and operating system; tracking the number of visitors on this site; and understanding how visitors use our site.

We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

## SSL Technology

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that allows us to encrypt sensitive information you input at 128-bit strength. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology is presently the safest way to send credit card information over the Internet. Information is first encrypted on your computer and then decrypted on our server, preventing anyone from accessing any information in between. This is often symbolized on most web-browsers by a small padlock appearing on the bottom bar of the window and the prefix of the URL changing from http:// to https://. This indicates that a secure connection has been established.

## Your Account Information

When creating an account with GulAhmedShop.com, you'll be asked to provide a personal password. You will be required to use your chosen password for all future access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. Gul Ahmed reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in its sole discretion.

## Electronic Communication

Your email address is used to contact you concerning inquiries before, during and after your order is placed. We also use your email address to inform you of our new products, services and offers. You can opt out of such marketing communications at any time. All marketing email and direct mail communications, such as sale emails, newsletters and exclusive special offers, have easy-to-follow instructions on how to stop receiving them.

## Errors

We try our best to provide accurate information on our site. However, there may be times when some information on the site is inaccurate, out-of-date or incomplete. We apologize for such errors; but if we receive orders for products for which the listed cost is erroneously lower than the actual price, we will not be able to process such orders as it will not be feasible for us to sell those items below our cost or take a loss on freight charges.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

  * By E-Mail: customerservice@gulahmedshop.com
  * By Phone: +92-21-111 485 485 Ext-6510, 6542, 6536,6521,6518

## Policy Changes

Our business changes constantly and we will continue to implement new technologies to improve the services and features we provide. As a consequence, the terms in this Privacy Policy may change also. All such changes and additions will be posted here promptly. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. This policy was posted in September 2015.

Please check our website frequently to see recent changes.
